http://catholicmarketing.com/content/820904/1/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy - Catholic Marketing
Products
Vendors
Search
ARE YOU A MEMBER?
0Cart
ARE YOU A MEMBER?
Privacy Policy
This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site. We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
Information Collection And Use
While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include but is not limited to your name ("Personal Information").
Log Data
Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. In addition, we may use third-party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze the data.
Communications
We may use your Personal Information to contact you with email, newsletters, marketing or promotional materials.
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your computer's hard drive. Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy subjected to variations in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page. We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time, and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the changes and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
The Catholic Marketing Network helps everyone connect with organizations and individuals who serve the needs of Catholics. Are you a Business or Ministry? JOIN NOW by selecting the CMN Membership level that's right for you.
Meet Our Members
Service Providers
Catholic Bookstores
Publishers
Ministries
Product Suppliers
Media
Other Services
Our Lady of Guadalupe: Patroness of the Catholic Marketing Network. Viva Guadalupe!
Catholic Marketing Network P.O. Box 610465 Dallas, Texas 75261Phone:
+1 800 506 6333
About Us
Contact Us
Follow with us
Copyrights ©2020. All Rights Reserved. Terms and Conditions | Privacy Policy
